A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Advance Office, Series 1 FA781
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Events, 1975-1976; 1
  - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, KS (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 August (Box 13, Folder 222)
  - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, KS (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 August (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Republican National Convention Hearings, Kansas City, MO, 1976 August 9 (Box 13, Folder 224)
  - President Ford Strategy Meeting, Vail, Colorado, 1976 August 26-27 (Box 13, Folder 225)
  - Senator Robert Stafford Reception, Woodstock, VT, 1976 September 28 (Box 14, Folder 226)
  - Campaign 1976, 1976 September (Box 14, Folder 227)
  - Vice Presidential Staff Party, Washington, D. C., 1976 September 8 (Box 14, Folder 228)
  - Roy Wilkens' NAACP Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 September 10 (Box 14, Folder 229)
  - Senator Ted Steven's Moose Roast, Washington, D. C., 1976 September 15 (Box 14, Folder 230)
  - New York State Blitz, Buffalo to New York City (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 September 16 (Box 14, Folder 231)
  - New York State Blitz, Buffalo to New York City (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 September 16 (Box 14, Folder 232)
  - New York State Blitz, Buffalo to New York City (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 September 16 (Box 14, Folder 232A)
  - Jim Thompson for Governor Dinner, Chicago, IL, 1976 September 21 (Box 14, Folder 233)
  - Jim Thompson for Governor Dinner, Chicago, IL, 1976 September 21 (Box 14, Folder 233A)
  - Ohio Blitz, Cleveland, Columbus, Cincinnati, 1976 September 22 (Box 14, Folder 234)
  - New Jersey/Pennsylvania Blitz, Morris County, Philadelphia, Erie, Pittsburgh (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 September 28-29 (Box 14, Folder 235)
  - New Jersey/Pennsylvania Blitz, Morris County, Philadelphia, Erie, Pittsburgh (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 September 28-29 (Box 15, Folder 236)
  - American Indian Art Exhibition, London, England, 1976 October 3-5 (Box 15, Folder 237)
  - Dole/Rockefeller Dinner, Chicago, IL, 1976 October 7 (Box 15, Folder 238)
  - Columbus Day Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 October 9 (Box 15, Folder 239)
  - Salute to the President Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 October 12 (Box 15, Folder 240)
  - California/Oregon/Washington Sweep (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 October 12-14 (Box 15, Folder 241)
  - California/Oregon/Washington Sweep (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 October 12-14 (Box 15, Folder 242)
  - Labor Leader Meeting, New York, NY, 1976 October 15 (Box 15, Folder 243)
  - Michigan/Minnesota Sweep (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 October 18-19 (Box 15, Folder 244)
  - Michigan/Minnesota Sweep (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 October 18-19 (Box 15, Folder 245)
  - Michigan/Minnesota Sweep (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 October 18-19 (Box 15, Folder 245A)
  - Emily DuPont's Reception for Senator Bill Roth, Wilmington, DE, 1976 October 21 (Box 16, Folder 246)
  - Children with Learning Disabilities, Washington, D. C., 1976 October 21 (Box 16, Folder 247)
  - National Press Club Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 October 26 (Box 16, Folder 248)
  - Nassau County Blitz, NY (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 October 27 (Box 16, Folder 249)
  - Nassau County Blitz, NY (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 October 27 (Box 16, Folder 250)
  - Williamsburg Foundation Dinner, Williamsburg, VA, 1976 November 12 (Box 16, Folder 251)
  - Republican Eagles Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 November 16 (Box 16, Folder 252)
  - Symposium on "Future of Product", Washington, D. C., 1976 November 16 (Box 16, Folder 253)
  - 22nd Annual Session - NATO, Williamsburg, VA, 1976 November 18 (Box 16, Folder 254)
  - China Institute in North America Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 November 30 (Box 16, Folder 255)
  - Founding of Pakistan Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1976 December 2 (Box 16, Folder 256)
  - Visit of Prime Minister of Italy, Giulio Andreotti, Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 December 7 (Box 16, Folder 257)
  - Georgetown Graduate Student Forum, Washington, D. C., 1976 December 8 (Box 16, Folder 258)
  - National Defense University Address, Fort McNair, Washington, D. C., 1976 December 9 (Box 16, Folder 259)
  - National Capital Area Political Science Association Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1976 December 4 (Box 16, Folder 260)
  - Funeral for Mayor Richard Daley, Chicago, IL, 1976 December 22 (Box 16, Folder 261)
- Vice Presidential Staff Correspondence, 2
  - Pending Invitations, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 262)
  - Allison, Dick, 1975 September-October (Box 16, Folder 263)
  - Herter, Susan, In, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 264)
  - Herter, Susan, Out, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 265)
  - Huldrum, Kathy, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 266)
  - Military Office, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 267)
  - Morrow, Hugh, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 268)
  - Pagnotta, Frank, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 269)
  - Perisco, Joe, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 270)
  - Kightlinger, Jack, VP Photographer, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 271)
  - Vice Presidential Staff, General, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 272)
  - Towell, Nancy, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 273)
  - U. S. Secret Service (USSS), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 274)
  - Wallison, Peter, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 275)
  - Whitman, Ann, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 276)
  - Administrative Details, Advance Office, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 277)
  - Advance Schedule, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 278)
  - Letters/Memoranda to Advancemen, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 279)
  - Advancemen-Resumes, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 280)
  - Advancemen-Resumes, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 280A)
  - Volunteer Advancemen, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 281)
  - Advancement, Travel Expenses, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 282)
  - Vice Presidential Air Craft Configurations (Box 17, Folder 283)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Biography & Record, 1973, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 284)
  - Correspondence Procedures, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 285)
  - Limousine Services, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 286)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 287)
  - Office Procedures, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 288)
  - Photograph, Vice Presidential Seal (Box 17, Folder 289)
  - Points of Interest in Washington, DC (Box 17, Folder 290)
  - Press Office Notice, Baggage Tags-Press, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 291)
  - Diagrams of Speaking Areas (Box 17, Folder 292)
  - Campaign Volunteers, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 293)
  - White House Communications Agency, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 294)
  - Parties, Vice President's Residence, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 295)
  - Vice President's Residence House Warming Party, Guest List, #1, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 296)
  - Vice President's Residence House Warming Party, Guest List, #2, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 297)
  - Margaretta F. Rockefeller Schedules, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 298)
  - Admiral's House, Vice President's Residence, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 299)
  - Admiral's House, Vice President's Residence, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 299A)
  - Margaretta F. Rockefeller, B'nai B'rith Reception, Washington, D C, 1975 March 9 (Box 18, Folder 300)